Hi guys, hi, Nisha. Oh my gosh to see you. It's been crazy, Nisha. I
Don't know
Kind of hanging in there
but
Do you like the Bible? I like I've been reading these Psalms. Hey dingle
I'm gonna read I want to read a few Psalms and maybe I'll do another panel, but
There's a really short one, Psalm 43.
I just get the number in my head and I pick this up.
I didn't know it said necessarily,
but we'll see if it like resonates with the chat.
Hey everybody, hi Dingle.
I know, isn't that crazy?
It's your major malfunction, Joe.
Yeah, okay, so Psalm 43, okay?
It says,
Vindicate me, my God, and plead my cause against an unfaithful nation.
Rescue me from those who are deceitful and wicked.
You are, God, my stronghold.
Why have you rejected me?
Why must you go about mornings, oppressed by the enemy?
Send me your light and your faithful care.
Let them lead me.
Let them bring me to your holy mountain, to a place where you dwell.
And I will go to the altar of God.
To God to my joy and delight. I will praise you with the liar. Oh God my God
Why my soul? Are you downcast? Why are you so disturbed within me?
Put your hope in God for I will yet praise him my savior. Am I God?
Well, who's the red horse by name?
That's a red horse
the name are you talking about the cat like the
the black cat and they're in the
I know in the red it's red and black it should be in a horse
I'm a good host. Thank you guys. I was just you know feeling a little back to the living guys do your thing
Okay, now I now 49 came to my head
Maybe like five of these. I
Didn't know yeah, Joe's daddy. Yeah, Joe's a full diamonds boyfriend. Okay for the director of music of
the sons of Korah Assam
Hmm it says hear this all you peoples listen all who live in this world
Both low and high, rich and poor like, my mouth will speak words of wisdom.
The meditation of my heart will give you understanding.
I will turn my ear to a proverb, with the harp I will expound my riddle.
Why should I fear when evil days come, when wicked deceivers surround me?
Those who trust in their wealth and boast of their great riches.
No one can redeem the life of another or give to God a ransom for them.
The ransom for life is costly, no payment is ever enough, so that they should live on
forever and not see decay, for all can see that the wise die and the foolish and senseless
their houses forever, their dwellings for endless generations,
though they had named lands after themselves.
People, despite their wealth, do not endure.
They are like beasts that perish.
This is the fate of those who trusted themselves
and of their followers who approved their sayings.
They are like sheep and are destined to die.
Death will be their shepherd,
but the upright will prevail over them in the morning.
Their forms will decay in the grave far from their princely mansions, but God will redeem me from the realm of the dead
He will surely take me to himself. Do not be over
odd when others grow rich when the splendor
Splendor of their houses increases
for they will take nothing with them when they die. Their splendor will not descend with them.
Though while they live, they count themselves blessed, and people praise you. When you prosper,
they will join those who have gone before them, who will never again to the light of life.
People who have wealth but lack understanding are like beasts that perish.
Oh, thank you, Joe. I'm glad you liked it.
We belong together. I'll just read two more. Let me see. Diana song
What's the number guys? Oh
Some 72, okay
Okay
Are you enjoying these I like these are beautiful it says some 72 it says
Give the king thy judgments, O God, and thy righteousness unto the king's son.
He shall judge thy people with righteousness and the poor with judgment.
The mountains shall bring peace to the people and the little hills by righteousness.
He shall judge
the poor of the people. He shall save the children of the needy and he shall break up in pieces the oppressor.
They shall fear thee as long as the sun and moon endure throughout all generations.
He shall come down like rain upon the mown grass as showers that water the earth.
In his days shall the righteous flourish in abundance of peace so long as the moon endure.
They that dwell in the wilderness shall bow before him, and his enemies shall kick the dust, lick the dust, I'm sorry.
The kings of Tarshish and of the Isles shall bring presents. The kings of
Sheba and Sherba shall after opera gifts.
Yeah, all kings shall fall down before him, all nations shall serve him, for he shall deliver the needy when he cries.
The poor also and him that hath no helper.
He shall spare the poor and needy, and shall save the souls of the needy.
He shall redeem their souls from deceit and violence and precious shall their blood be
in his sight.
And he shall live, and to him shall be given.
the gold of Sheba. Prayer also shall be made for him continually and daily shall
he be praised. There shall be a handful of corn in the earth upon the top of the
mountains. The fruit thereof shall shake the lake Lebanon and they of the city
shall flourish like grass of the earth. His name shall endure forever. His name
shall be continued as long as the sun and men shall be blessed in them. In him
Blessed be the Lord God, the God of Israel, who only do with wondrous things, and blessed
be the glorious name for ever, and let the whole earth be filled with His glory. Amen
and amen. The prayers of David and the Son of Jesse are ended.
You fell asleep? I'm just reading some nice prayers. You like your reading? Nice.
Yeah, how's everyone? Hey, I guess who's here? Hey, wake up Jamie. Like who's here?
Who's here?
Miss Lenore. I love you.
Amen. Well, there's already a couple more. They're so good. I'm gonna 85, okay?
The numbers are just coming to my head, okay?
This is a short one, let's go, okay.
Will you prolong your anger through all generations?
Will you not revive us again that your people may rejoice in you?
Show us your unfilling love, Lord, and grant us your salvation.
I will listen to what God the Lord says.
He promises peace to his people, his faithful servants, but let them not turn to folly.
Surely his salvation is near those who fear him, that his glory may dwell in our land.
Love and faithfulness meet together righteousness and peace kiss each other
Faithfulness springs forth from the earth and righteousness looks down from heaven
Lord will indeed give what is good and our land will yield its harvest
Righteousness goes before him and prepares his way for steps
Hi guys
You do tarot cards and read the Bible with the fuck is this?
Yeah, well, if you're familiar with the Psalms, you know, the Bible is a lot of collected
It's a lot of collected things
That is and so even if you're not
Chris, I mean it's like it's like a lot of it's a mix of a kind of things, okay, and the songs are very magical
So I think they're all compatible
Hi, baby
Cats are better. Oh Joe. Hi babes
Are you coming kisses you give me kisses your little lover, huh?
He's sitting on my shoulder. You're sitting on my you can't sit on my shoulder. Hey, baby. I
Love you, too
See her
Hi, I flirty
Yeah, yeah, I flirty demon
So, yeah, I got I was I heard a little bit of the the panel
Yeah, it was kind of
Yeah, I do read the Bible it was a little bit I would say, you know
It's kind of it's a little bit, you know sad how
Transphobic this society is I think
But I'm really hope it's changing for the better for
For all people if I make a wish I would like you to
Read
Something from the Talmud? Hold on.
I'm sorry. Yeah, how do you spell that? G?
G-I-T-I-N from the Talmud. Oh look what up. I'll see. I've read a lot of the Talmud.
It's kind of interesting. It's the Jewish oral tradition. They had the
Torah
which is written into the first five books of the Bible.
But then they have the oral tradition called the Talmud and the Talmud
And you spell it. Hold on
You to read
G can you start g i t i m?
Okay, I see it I don't know how long it is. Let me check
Okay, it's quite long, but I'll read it a little bit.
If I can find it.
Okay.
So this is from the Talmud, okay?
Talmud is full of these, you know, there's a Babylonian Talmud,
but the oral tradition continued because the Jews loved Babylon.
Okay, so this is Gitan 2 through 8, okay?
It says Rob, which is rabbi, rabbi shista said a person should never cause an
atmosphere of excessive fear of him in his home because
Because the husband of the Pilagesh in Giva caused her excessive fear of him, which led to the death of tens of thousands of Jews.
Pilagesh did that provoked her husband's excessive wrath, and the final chapters of the Book of Judges teach and detail how the relationship eventually led to a civil war within the Jewish people that resulted in tens of thousands of battlefield deaths.
The halacha is codified in Rambam's Mishneh Torah, Laws of Marriage, 2519.
concludes by saying there is an oppressive atmosphere in the home will eventually lead
to three major sins, forbidden, intimate relations, spilling of blood, and desecration
of Shabbat of Shabbat. Rabbi Nyu Shaonal substitutes the secretion of the name of God
as the third term in the list. So here it is. It says,
Rabbi Abatu said, a person should never cause an atmosphere of excessive fear of him in his home, because a great man did this and was even fed a great thing, i.e. forbidden food.
The Jamara identifies the great man as Rabbi Shamina Ben Gamilil and the forbidden food as a limb from a live animal.
Not one from an animal after a shashita our
Gamara questions the statement based on a rule that God does not cause a righteous person to sin due to the actions of his
animal and
And all the more so would not have a stumbling
Block of prohibited foods put in front of a righteous person without his knowing it was forbidden. So how could this?
happened. The Jamara answers that he didn't actually eat it. It was merely offered to him to eat. And he refused to eat it. Although he did not know it was not kosher.
Rashi explains that this non-kosher limb was brought to him since the original kosher food was lost and due to fear of the negative repercussions since there was a fear in the air.
of his home the lost kosher food was hurly replaced with a non-kosher food
I don't know if that's what you want me to read, but you know it's interesting they're eating them eating a live limb
That's what's forbidden. You should not be eating a live limb for any animal. I'm glad they put that in there
Really doing a darling. That is not
Good
Get it. I don't please don't eat any you know live animals arm
it's forbidden please and
Do not cause an atmosphere of fear because that will attract these I guess these things
Interesting I mean, it's yeah, I think I guess there's I don't know if I read the right one. What's up, Nikki?
Misha needs food stands for 10 people. Oh my gosh
I would date Nisha, but don't have enough food stamps.
Nisha, put the food, try chicken,
and start picking up a book.
Yeah, Nisha, you should learn tarot too, Nisha.
Everyone's learning it now.
I think I've inspired like a whole panel,
panel versus people to take up tarot.
I think everyone's falling in love
and that was kind of my goal.
Wow, 30, you are being so, oh no, 30 is fine.
Niki's a real woman.
Yeah.
There's really interesting things I can think of, but I don't know, I want to talk to you for a minute.
How is it doing? Occasionally, like, they need to hash out on panels.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm probably tweaking the format of the show a little bit.
I mean, the panels are...
Think I've been I think it's a little bit too much panel a little bit too much stress, but I think Joe
Don't just go straight so he wouldn't date me. I probably would date him
Lurie, why are you trying to hurt my feeling? Oh?
Hi rogue
Hi, Nikki. Hi, I saw you. See ya
Yeah, so let's see where's tobacco somewhere. I forgot some smoke cigar
Hope you had a good day at Saturday morning try to think of something to share
Let's see
Okay, I
Have a book
This is like so this is like the first published
Novel in the world like the first kind of novel actual in that they have the full novel of it's from Rome is
Called the golden ass and it's by Apolaus. Okay?
It's a really good book. So if you guys know my name is psyche
The story of Cupid and psyche is actually told
think they're the first time in this story it's kind of put in the middle of
the book it's not in this copy because this isn't a bridge copy of the rest of
the book because the Cupid and Psyche story is
the Cupid and Psyche story is very long okay so
I'll read the first chapter maybe I'll go through and I'll read the whole book like you know
event like through the weeks and stuff but I'll try to just read some of the first chapter until
it gets higher oh yeah it's just a few pages okay here we go okay so it says Thessaly the land of
magic so Thessaly is in Greece it was known as the land of magic right and it says but listen
I am going to whisper seductively in your ear about my travels around Greece with a little
I'm a Greek who came to Rome and learned Latin, which was torture.
So I hope you will forgive me if I'm a rough and even brain kind of speaker.
The linguistic transformation fits the subject of metamorphosis in my tale.
I will begin.
Pay attention.
You'll be entertained.
I was going to Thessaly on business, though I was also hoping to experience the magic
and sorcery for which it was so well known.
It's from there I traced my distinguished lineage on my mother's side, from the famous
Clutarch and sexist to philosopher's nephew.
I have passed through every steep mountains and slippery valleys, dew-damped plowlands
and fertile plains, riding a native pure white horse.
and I leapt down onto my feet to shake off the sitting fatigue by strolling. I wiped my horse's
sweat from his brow, carefully rubbed his forehead, massaged his ears, let the rains fall free,
and guided him to a gentle slope where he could dispel his tiredness with the stomach's natural
fortification of food. He had his walking breakfast, leaning his head down as he munched the meadows
I had a letter of introduction.
to one Milo of Haipata.
So when I came to the first inn along the way,
I approached an old woman, the innkeeper,
and I asked her whether the city was Haipata.
He nodded, and I asked.
Do you know of a certain Milo, one of the foremost citizens?
She laughed and said he really is the foremost
since he lives right there before the city gates.
Joking aside, good woman, I said,
could you tell me who he is and what house he lives in?
Do you see those windows in the distance that look like out on the town, and the other side
the doors facing the alley nearby? The Milo you're looking for lives there. He's plenty wealthy,
richer than anyone, but he's notorious for its extreme stinginess and shabby squalor.
Gauge's high interest on enormous loans, demanding deposits of gold and silver,
but he stays shut up inside his sparse house, obsessed with rusting coins, along with his wife,
The partner of his wretched existence, plus he doesn't have any domestic help other than
one little slave girl, and he always walks around dressed like a beggar.
Now it was my turn to laugh.
My friend Demias sure did think ahead and provide kindly for my journey when he connected
me with someone like this.
No worry about smoke and cooking fumes.
As I spoke, I moved a little further until I reached the doorway and started to knock
vociferously on the firmly bolted door.
Finally a cute young woman came out and said, Hey you, you knocking so hard on my door.
On what terms do you want to take out alone?
Or are you only one who doesn't know that we only accept gold and silver as collateral?
Well, that's an inauspicious beginning, I said, Could you just tell me whether your master
is home?
but why do you want to know? I have a letter for him from Demias of Corinch.
Wait here while I announce you, she said, disappearing inside, bolting the doors again,
but after a moment she came back and opened the house for me, saying,
he requests you. I enter and find him reclining on a pittifly tiny couch,
just about to eat dinner, with his wife sitting at his feet. There was a table set out, empty,
which he gestured toward and then he announced welcome and help yourself.
Thanks, I replied and immediately handed him Demia's letter. He read it quickly.
I am grateful for my friend Demias for commending to me such a distinguished guest.
With these words he commanded his wife to move and ordered me to sit in her place.
When I hesitated out of politeness, he grabbed the edge of my tunic and barked,
We can't acquire any seeding or even adequate furniture. So I sat and he continued
I would have guessed rightly just from your proud carriage and
exceptional personal beauty as well as from your
Virginal modesty that you are descended from aristocratic lineage
But my friend Demias affirms that in his letter. So I ask that you not spurn the tightness of our little
Hubble see there the next room will be a respectable retreat for you have a pleasant stay with us
You make our house greater by your distinguished status and glory resounds to you
If you are content with our meager establishment and with that he called his slave girl
Lotus pick up our guest baggage and
Stow it carefully in that bedroom there and while you're at it get to the storeroom and bring out
oil for rubbing, towels for drying, and all the rest he needs, quickly, and guide my guest
to the nearest baths he's tired from a very long and arduous trip.
When I heard this, I reflected on Milo's stinginess, and wanted to ingratiate myself
with him yet further, so I interrupted.
I don't need any of it.
All that I need when I travel and I could easily acquire about the baths really what is the most important thing for me?
Photos take these coins and purchase hay and barley for my horse who carried me here briskly
When that was all done and my things have been stowed in my room. I went to the baths by myself
This is called the golden ass and this is by Apollos. It's a it's a novel
It's one of the oldest books in the world and it's really about magic and transformation met up
It's got a lot of magic. It's really cool
So after my bath, I returned to Milo's house and retreated to my room.
But there, then I encountered Photis, the maid servant.
The host is asking for you, she said, since I had already experienced Milo's absentee-nessness,
travels should be soothed, not by food, but by sleep. But when Milo heard my
refusal, he barged in himself, grabbed my hand, and started to tug me along
slowly. While I delayed and resisted somewhat, he insisted, I will not leave
until you follow me. I swear by the gods. So in obedience to his obscenity, and
against my will, I was led to that tiny couch of his,
where he sat me down. How is our friend Deminus faring, and his wife, his children? How about his
slaves? I responded to each query. Next he asked me very meticulously about the reasons for my journey.
After I laid it all out, thoroughly he still had more questions about my city and its leaders,
and finally about the governor himself, probing with unparalleled sharpness.
When he noticed that I, after such a rough journey and the additional stress of the series
of tales, was sleepily trailing off in the midst of my sentences, and in my tiredness
was babbling in distinct portals of words, he finally allowed me to go to bed.
I escaped over the time, being the clamorous and starvational dinner party of a putrid old
man and returned to my room, giving myself up to the sleep I longed for.
Okay, sorry loose asshole. I'm sorry. Yeah, yeah, I mean the story gets better. I mean, I mean, that's the beginning. I would just want to go through the whole book eventually, but hold on.
But, you know what happens? I'll spoil a little bit. He wants to play with magic. And so we asked that slave girl to go, you know, there's a mistress of the house is like a witch writer name is Pamphile.
I don't want to spoil it, I just want to tell you what happens soon.
She can turn into an owl by rubbing this stuff on her body, so he's like, give me some of
that salve and rub it on me, I want to turn into an owl too.
You've heard, oh you love the story, Ilia?
And so, and then she gets the wrong salve or she rubs it on wrong, I don't know, he
turns into a donkey and then, that's just a sample of what happens later in the book,
soon, okay?
You'll love it. How are you guys doing? I know I know it's not not everyone's cup of tea, but this is you know my cup of tea and
Maybe you'll learn or you'll learn about something you ever heard of and you'll be interesting
Hey kitty cats. Hey look at the cat
Hi
Thank you cats
Okay, well, thank you for hanging out with me
Ah, you've been through the desert. I've been through the desert on a horse with no name
Guys I love stories and a million of them, but I'm gonna roll them out very slowly telling you them
But I have I do have probably a lifetime of those stories to tell you
As long as you're as long as you hang out with me
Always have stories. That's how I started my channel
The stories
What's a blue pass? Oh?
You know I say hi to Lola Lola. Can we see your RBF?
Lola. Hey, Lenore. Can you come say hi, Lenore?
Lenore, come say hi. Where have you been?
Hi.
You're being pretty. I miss Lenore.
Oh, is that good? Oh, your ear, your ear.
What, you want some too? You want to say hi, too?
Oh, come on, Tracy. Tracy, you say hi, too.
Everyone loves you. Hi. I'm a lucky, I'm a lucky guy with all these cats. Lucky man.
Yeah, so I hope you're doing good. Let me just see. I want to tell you about the energies on the
summer solstice because we just had it yesterday, right? And it was very
Weird day and so is I don't know. It's like the hot the longest day of the year. Maybe
But he has the blackest eyes the devil's eyes. It was that oh, yeah, I'm rosemary's baby, right?
Rose Maddie's baby one of my best. Okay, we're the best. Okay, let's see
Where's not here, let's see
The what the summer solstice energies were
Okay
So it's also called midsummer guys, I don't know if you ever seen this movie called midsummer. Oh, wow, it's a weird movie
It's by the guy that did this movie called a hereditary
So it says the Earth tilts closest to the Sun every year between June 20th 21st
Marking the longest day of the year of the Northern atmosphere and the first official first day of summer
This article is about the summer solstice astrology and how it's celebrated
Okay
It says
At the summer solstice, the sun appears to stand still.
The word solstice derives from the soul, sun, and cister, standing still.
For about three days, the sun appears to stop in its tracks.
In actuality, its relative position to the earth doesn't change much, hence the illusion.
From our vantage point, the northern hemisphere, the sun is finishing its northbound journey
The summer solstice marks the start of cancer season in astrology. At the summer solstice,
the sun appears to pass directly over the tropic of cancer. This is the moment
when astrologers say the sun has entered cancer, meaning that it's now traveling
through the part of the zodiac band represented by cancer.
It says the zodiac signs haven't shifted the constellations have
Periodically astronomers will announce
Breaking news that horoscopes aren't accurate because the constellations have shifted or they will announce a 13th zodiac sign
citing the constellation of bicus and claim that the horoscope dates
Far for your zodiac sign have changed wrong. That says NASA said it's not true. Okay
Solstice is a good day to balance energies. Oh shit, I need to flip my phone in.
So good day to balance energies. And so, you know, balancing energies, that's like the temperance where it's like you take, you know, if you do some alchemy, you can take, you can balance like
masculine, feminine, you can do, you can, it's a good day to balance all your energies. One common misconception, hold on, so let me see.
It says, in astrology, the sun is associated with the active Yang principle, but here's
the paradox.
The Cancer zodiac sign rules the receptive yin principle and is governed by the emotional
moon.
So we have a forthright sun stopping in its tracks to usher in a new, flowing solar cycle.
This is an ideal time to consider ways which we can balance the yin and yang forces in
our lives.
Where could you yank it up and put more action-oriented, decisive energy?
We all contain both energies within us in an age where humans are becoming more fluid and
redefined than ever. The summer solstice is an awesome moment to widen our notions of what that means for us.
It says, Solstice rituals date to ancient Egypt, Roman Stonehenge.
In ancient Egypt, summer solstice coincided with the first bays of the Nile's flooding,
marking the Egyptian New Year.
In ancient China, they celebrated the switch from yin to yin energy for the next half a
year.
The Romans honored the goddess Vesta, one of astrology's major asteroids, with their
vestalia solstice suare.
at their solstice cronia festival where slaves and free people feast it as equals for the day.
Okay, so I don't know if that's interesting to you. I mean, it's just, I guess it just says
balance your energies that day. It just seems like maybe if it says balance the energies,
it would say maybe the energies will go off balance, you can see where you need to balance it.
I can read the horoscopes for the year.
Okay.
Okay, well, I'll just read the general horoscope.
So, you guys are enjoying this.
Okay.
Happy summer solstice. On June 20th, the longest day of the year in these northern hemisphere, a
blissful new season of radical honesty and love is set to arrive.
Okay.
The Spirit Driving Sun
will enter the empathic camps around this day,
urging us to focus on nurturing our closest connections.
Domestic pleasures are sure to attract our interests
during this period as well,
giving us the chance to explore our inner worlds
and reclaim our creativity as we cozy up
to those who make us feel most secure.
Just try to be mindful of moodiness
cropping up in yourself and others, moodiness, right?
I think a lot of people have been moody a little bit lately.
As this transit can sometimes make us more sensitive
in our interactions with the ones we love, not true.
Starting July 4th, when dreamy Neptune stations retrograde
in spontaneous areas, we called it to take
off our rose-colored glasses and see ourselves and our circumstances for what they truly are.
As the planet of illusion and delusion moves in reverse over the next six months,
it's best to avoid taking big swings. Instead, seek to plant your feet firmly on the ground
and pay attention to the facts that come to light under this helpful influence.
They can help guide your decisions with sobering clarity.
Exciting changes could be on the horizon when visionary Uranus
The Planetary Rebellion will spend the next four months traveling through the mutable
air sign which could heighten our collective brain power and make us yearn to express ourselves
without limits.
It's important to stay alert under this energy as monumental developments can happen quickly
and you might even stumble upon an innovation that could propel society forward.
Be ready to move your life in a new direction.
You'll be wise to mind your manners and watch out for miscommunication as Mercury, Messenger
stations retrograders and proud Leo July 17th.
Depending on your time zone, under this influence, it's easy to get caught up in an unnecessary
conflict if you don't pay attention to crucial details, so do your best to avoid showboating,
triple-check your facts, and choose your words carefully until Mercury's station is
directed on August 11th, doing so could help save you from major embarrassment and confusion.
Then prepare for a collective confident boost as the ego-ruling sun enters Expressive Leo
Over the next four weeks of transit, our inner performers will be eager to come out to play,
and we may feel driven to pour more of our attention into our passion projects and image
as a result. Use this energy to celebrate what makes you unique and explore activities that
let you shine from within. Just be mindful that the shadow side of Leo's season can sometimes
make us act a little narcissistic. Resist falling in love with your own reflection and remember
Just squeeze a huge chair. Oh my god. I
Don't want to know that. Thank you for that coming on camera doing that. Okay
On August 22nd, the set will move into meticulous Virgo, inviting us to reorganize our lives
from top to bottom under the influence of the mutable earth sign.
We're often able to see the world in more straightforward terms, making it easier to
declutter our minds and homes by separating what's useful and what's not.
There's also a beautiful time to organize your schedule so you can make the most out
of the last stretch of summer.
Or get a head start on planning the season ahead.
You could be tempted to delve into all kinds of enticing mysteries when unpredictable Uranus
and curious Gemini's sex tiles outwardly meptune and passionate Aries on August 28.
These planets haven't created a sex tile since 1968, making this a rare and remarkable aspect.
Seize the chance to really think about how you fit into the bigger picture and recognize
the importance of collective awareness. Positive changes can happen when we make an
effort to clear the fog and take meaningful steps towards creating a more harmonious future.
Finally, be sure to listen to your instincts when Revolutionary Uranus stations retrograde
an Inquisitive Gemini September 5th.
Uranus will spend the next five months moving in reverse, helping us to stand up for ourselves
and take ownership of the stories we want to tell.
This is an ideal moment to focus on self-evolution and experiment with new ideas for the future.
Start thinking about what you'd like to leave behind in order to truly grow.
I hope you like that.
Well, well, that's crazy
If anyone wants me to read I don't know if there's anyone listening still. I know I know I think quiet
I want to read your primal astrology if anyone wants to give me their Chinese zodiac and their Western
No regular zodiac sign or Sun sign
The combination of those two creates another sign. It's a whole different animal
There's an interesting information anyone wants me to I don't know. I think I might have
Might have put you guys to sleep. I'm sorry. I was just I was just reading
It's uh, wow
You know in the past six months, I've done I've talked more to people I've them talked more than I ever have in my entire life
I've never talked. I'm usually silent most of the time
I've been talking so much like I've said I've said everything. I've said everything
Wow guys, it's journey
Thanks for spending it with me
Thanks for putting up with me
Hello, hello, then hello, how are you? Hello greetings
Greetings, sir. How are you tonight or this morning? Pretty good
good
Yeah, it's just it's like what time is it? It's 307 a.m.
Los Angeles
Where is everybody?
Well, I did start I was starting to read from like a book and stuff because you know, I like stories and stuff
I don't know. I think it scares some people away, but it is a good story
Or maybe I put them to sleep.
I'm not sure.
But it looks like they're waking up, 15 people in the chat.
We'll get them, we'll get them woke up.
Now that the panel going, it's not just me.
I think people are bored of me.
Hey, what's up to digital Zenizen, allegedly?
How's everyone in the chat?
Yeah, Joe.
Okay, yeah, we got a good, improved diamonds here.
Yeah, so, interesting panel tonight.
It's nice and calm.
Ilya likes it. Yeah, it was just a little bit crazy today. I don't know if you saw some of their shows earlier
You know
You know really love Bita and she's she's so mad at me and
It seems like she hates me and it's like it's a it's confusing me
They're ahead of us. Are you there?
Yeah, I'm here. It's a
But what is it 6 a.m. And on the East Coast? Oh, you're in the East Coast. Okay, cool
I'm on the West Coast. Oh, you're in the West Coast
Yeah
Yeah, be this man at me, too. Oh, she is. Yeah
Well, is that you're like regular so you're Dennis? No, no, this isn't my regular
So is it like the lattice thing is like the oh, that's okay. It's not the lattice
Okay, so but you said you do you do know beat I don't know if you're the same guy. She was she was talking about do you practice you practice
Any the occult no, okay, I guess you're a different guy
Yeah, yeah, maybe I don't know
Beed hits your guys. Yeah, I don't know. I think there's a whole I think that we need to start recovery group for
People people be the people be
People who beat who beat it wants to beat up. I think we're the the beat up beat up group
But you know, I hope I hope everything's I hope everything will work
I don't know. Maybe I hope hopefully it's just like she's just in a bad mood or something
I just don't I just didn't understand
She was so mad at me, but be the ones to break. Oh, yeah, I know Joe
Yeah, is it TTP or TTP or TPP? I'm confused. That was TPP
You know TTP is hold on here. Yeah, the people's podcast. Oh, okay TPP. Yeah. Hey, easy
Yeah, yeah, that's my other page psyche as allegedly is me. Okay. Yeah
Yeah, so TPP is down
Yeah, someone was just talking about I just woke and I want to go check out someone's first
And she was like, I can't see no lives.
They took down his page and he out for 500 lives up
and all of them is gone.
His community is gone.
They must have took it down.
No more memberships.
You know what happens?
Yeah, that's what they say.
And I just woke up.
I don't know.
But there was no story about if they get porn bombed
or is there something said on which people don't know?
They did everything over there.
So eventually he caught up.
Okay, it's a stew of toss violations on a regular basis over there
Yeah, well, that's why I try to like
Keep my show kind of clean even though it's not I that's why I delete a lot of shows
But what my page got taken down right and I got it reactivated
These cameras on that's why I don't got nothing up there right now because YouTube for all the videos and everything private even the
community post
Yeah
We told him it wouldn't be good for his channel to run it the way he does
Who are you talking about the guy? Okay. Yeah, okay the guy that
Yeah, I told him it wasn't good for him either
He didn't like that so it kicked me
So I'm pocketed donation money letting up for Tijuana. Oh, yeah
Um, yeah, I mean people's podcasts. That's one of the first panels I visited. I had some people
Uh, or a lot of people from them from them come over here and stuff, you know
It's not well. It's a pretty popular podcast because it's on all night long. Nick Johnson's happy. Ha ha ha. We owe Delo so much shit from Dave
So anybody who goes panel hopping ends up there, even if they don't have a connection there, you know, just from searching
Yeah, open panel. He's do all I used to do search open panels
Yeah, and yeah, I get a lot of people coming in for open panels, too
I think that's a good way to bring in an audience, but you know open panels can be kind of dangerous
It's like you never you know, you never know who's gonna come on
What they're gonna say what's what's gonna happen or you know, who's for you who's against you
It's the wild wild west of YouTube. Yeah, I mean, I'm shocked. I'm still here. I really am. I'm shocked. I'm still here
Only thing I can say is it was a miracle. It's a miracle
There's so many things that could have there's so many things that could have happened that
Where we're taking it down, but well, I notice you don't really go after other people on your channel
It's like you gotta bring his own content conversation and everything like you don't attack nobody
notice you let the drama people hang out here as long as they're chill right so
that's kind of dangerous yeah it's nowhere near as dangerous as being one
of the dicks who's out there attacking everybody all the time that's gonna put
a target on you right
Yeah, well, it's like I kind of stay in my lane
I just you know and sometimes people call my show that from different panels
There's people's podcast people came in fighting and with other people and you know
There's all these rival factions on YouTube that they all seem to gather in my chat sometimes and start fighting and sanctuary
Yeah, it's like I want to keep you know
I'm trying to keep the sanctuary safe and a sanctuary for everybody where it's like you know
Everyone can come here as long as they're cool
It's like if someone starts acting out and starts fighting with the people it's you know
It's supposed to be a place where everyone can like you know come come to like come to like relax and rest
Well
Yeah, I do like I do my some drama is good and it's also but it's also part of like a healing process is talking things out
And so if there's good conversations, but if it's just like doxing and
You know slandering and name-calling and going after other people. It's like then that's that's that's another thing
I'm not I would never go after anybody. I'm not gonna even if they hate me
I'm not gonna have been dead against them. I'm just gonna stay in my land. I'm gonna
I'm not even going venturing up to other panels anymore. It's like
It's too hard for me. I'm just too recognizable and people to start attacking you everywhere. I go
Yeah, that's one way of video that they're like, oh see this is where this is where easy hangs out
Let's go. Let's just take down his page. Let's take down his page
Yeah
If you could bring me 12 beers and cigarettes, then I was like, well, chill for a little bit, because I'm still awake.
And she called me like, I can get you beer, but I'll give you a couple of my cigarettes.
And I'm like, no, no, no.
When I drink, I need a whole pack.
You know what I mean?
I need a whole pack of my own six.
I don't want to have to borrow like a beggar from you.
And she's like why I'm still showing up. I was on the wall in the fucking police then you're going to fucking jail, bitch
So I just want to be here. It's the last time I ever see you guys. I love you, bitch
Bye Joe, goodnight, you guys
Tell the cops if I never seen again that this is the last
I've been like you're innocent. Don't worry about it. I'll be like
Joe wants a free process
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, we're calling an ambulance. He'll be fine. Don't worry. You could get the way I missed that whole thing. What happened?
He can outrun her I think he said he called he said he was calling the police and then she'll feel like I don't know
He told her he'll call this funny with his wife. I
Think it's his friend. I'm not sure
Okay, I don't know. I think I think they I think they have sexual chemistry, but they're afraid to go all the way
I didn't kiss
Yeah
Yeah, well Crystal would say oh, she's like you showed me you told you told me that you thought that I was Kim
And I was like, does that even make sense?
I did, and I must have been joking, but it's so ridiculous.
I don't know, people don't understand jokes anymore.
I'm a jokester, so I like to laugh.
But a lot of people choose to get offended.
They can choose to get offended.
They can choose just to say it.
That's not funny, I'm an idiot, but they're like,
oh my God, I can't believe you said that.
People get so offended by stupid little words.
It's a currency in this culture here in the United States a fence. Oh, yeah fence
Yeah, and I really don't I don't even think it's like we have a lot of rights in the Constitution
I don't think being offended is a right like because you can you can be offended by anything
You can be offended by like a someone at Walmart, you know
They're you know, they're mini skirt and they're like 300 pounds and that they're wearing a miniskirt. That's offensive. I mean, but
I mean you be offended by anything. It's like anything
I'm offended by the ingredients in a Twinkie. I mean really that's offensive
Yeah, good. I mean, it's not even real whipped cream because it doesn't expire for like 20 years. And so seriously
Is that yeah, what is that half of Taylor Swift's catalog? I'm offended by
Have her catalog. Yeah, or just you Taylor Swift in general, right? I
Just wasn't sure how far I could go with that, you know, yeah at least half
So, you know
Just like I wish people would like you get a sense of humor so because it's like people are just like
There's a selective outrage because certain people can say something to somebody. No, and I understand it sometimes
You know, we take things our loved ones say more seriously than random people can say right, but I
Don't know we people seem to get like they let's let some people say say anything and then other people can't say anything so
some people get
Just have the n-word bitch in their vocabulary all the time. It's the same a million times or is like if someone says it once and it's like
Oh my god, I can't believe you called me that a bee
It's like right. It's like when they say it was time. Yeah double standards, right? Hey Jan's chicken army
Uh, it's the D guy name starts with the D. Okay. Does your name start with the D? Is dad's ticket on me, right?
Yeah, denizen.
Okay. Okay. Denizen. Yes, it's denizen. Yeah, okay.
Hi, hey, that's like citizen, but without the rights and freedoms.
Well, that's not yeah, well, that kind of sucks. I mean,
um
Up to look up the definition. Yeah, because they just sit without the right. So sometimes kind of like oh, this is a little pithy joke
I tell
That's a joke. Oh, yeah, it's not quite in
Okay, there's the kernel of truth in it and it's putting in an exaggerated way
Okay, it's a government a person admitted to a residence in a foreign country, especially as an alien. Okay
So, you know, it's an alien an alien. So it's like, you know
That's kind of like a legal alien, but maybe not a full sea of citizen or I'm not sure the multiple definitions apply to if you continue reading
Okay, let me check it out
Inhabitants or residents a person who regularly frequents a place
Habitue the denizens of a local bar
Anything adapted to a new place condition, etc. Such as an animal or plant not indigenous to a place but successfully naturalized
That's my favorite. You like that one. Yeah, keep it about a plant hole on animal or plant
Okay, not indigenous but successfully naturalized. Okay
British law, British law, an alien admitted to a residence and
to certain rights of citizenship in a country. This legal designation has been obsolete since the
first half of the 20th century. It says first recorded in 1425 through 75, late middle English,
Denny's San, okay, means the one within, inside on the inside. Okay, means an insider maybe?
Hi, you're you're an insider. Okay. Good. Hey, what's up girl? I'm all those things
Nice, you know, I think we're all maybe all denizens of this world because I don't know if we were even
Really naturally from here, but I think we don't basically they can you know alien farm or something like that
I don't know alien zoo rock from different places different. I certainly feel like a mutant around the rest of these folks
I don't know about you, sir
How are you cats?
How are Einstein and Aristotle?
Long gone long gone make in kitty heaven, hopefully oh
Those my childhood cats. Oh, I don't know. I just I was I came over here the other day
This is one of the strangest conversations. I mean tell the one lady was a bit tipsy
Yeah, oh beat is okay, I don't know why she hates me, but I
Don't know it got antagonistic a few times
Like I said like for our first like our first six months that we knew each other there was like never any conflict and then
Then started like every like a day and a half or a few days she'd be mad at me over like something and it's like
And I really didn't even know I don't know. It's just very confusing. Hey, what's what's going on?
Oh, you did the blanket love the blanket you're doing your pop-up
He's making biscuits and nuzzling at the same time. Yeah, I'm eating some biscuits. Where's my kitty cats?
Oh, I have a couple of tricks is over there
Got five cats in here
That's gosh, and this is mouse. Oh
Is that a Russian blue?
Well, I mean, he's he was a feral cat, but yeah, he's got Russian blue in him
Hey, Jan
Yeah, he said hey Jan CZ there. Oh, hey easy
Yeah, oh yeah, I was listening I was brushing my teeth now I'm gonna walk my ass to the store nice and slow
That one looks a little bit like Aristotle
I'm just in my big boy
All my boy babies
Now I want to get in bed with mom. I
Love cuddling with my cats in bed. It's my it's my little
My heaven
Yeah, familiar your breeze contempt psyche. What won't go away go away then Mikey. Don't be so familiar with me
Yeah
Don't be so familiar. Don't think you know don't think you know me
I love you. Where's the
Tricks is right there. I think the other cats are out cats have been out summer time
It's really warm tonight. It feels so warm. It must be like 80 degrees here right now. Oh
Okay, I know
Say again I asked Dennis and if he found himself a handmade yet
Handmaid. No, I haven't been looking though. So there's that
No, did you seem like a cool guy you seem like a nice conservative gentlemen
Conservative
Aren't you though? Well, I guess that depends on your definition
Are you guys maga or something?
No, I'm not I am you are okay. I am
I mean, I wouldn't mind making America great again
Order of the country. Oh, there's my other cat
Oh
You got a or I got an orange too. Your name is Rudy
Yeah, I grew up in a family of Republicans, you know
California Republicans probably like a little bit more more liberal than the rest of the country, but you know still
Being gay growing up. I'm pretty much under George W. Bush. You know is the my 20s and stuff
That's when I was most kind of
You know into the
Gay rights things and then he was like taking them all down. Hey, I wasn't a big fan
But I then after that I didn't really care about politics
Yeah, I thought Trump was my father loved Trump. He was a he just loved them. They're both German eyes and oh
Yeah, I'd love Trump. He was
He was really pointed my dad what my dad had cancer
When Trump was ran for his second election
I must have was so disappointed when he lost, he just knew, like, he just knew he was never
going to live to see him make president again, and he didn't, and he died that summer.
Oh, my gosh.
Yeah.
Because.
Well, that's okay.
I mean, wherever he's at, he can see him now, he'll be the president, so.
It's kind of similar to my dad like, you know, he passed away
That's April and I think I don't know if Trump was running. Yeah, I think Trump was running again by that time
Yeah, so he would have liked to see him in office. He was a he brought a smile to his face
and I would tell Joe Biden jokes and I would make fun of Joe Biden too. I thought it thought he was kind of
Comical and
that I think it makes me really mad that that he was that he was in first of all as somebody
who has had a aging parents you know I feel for the man because I'm like why are why is
his family doing this to him why are they not letting him just
You know age gracefully or what why are they doing this the second part of it is the media for four years?
The media told us that there was nothing wrong with Joe Biden even though we could see it
They gas lit an entire nation of people
You know that guy should have been our president wasn't he wasn't fit to serve
Kind of reminds me of
Let's see, there was a president, I don't know if it was Teddy Roosevelt, yeah, Teddy
Roosevelt, no, no.
Who isn't there was someone in the wheelchair Franklin Delano Roosevelt and then there was his wife kind of ran the country
Yeah, Franklin Delano Roosevelt was in the wheelchair, but
their
Raja Wilson was actually in a coma or something or
Dehabilitated for months and his wife ran. She signed all of the she signed all the things
And there was a whole big cover up. She was running the White House basically. She's the first woman president. What's your old son?
wife mm-hmm yeah and we a lot of people don't know that yeah but they yeah the
media very carefully orchestrates all the appearances and did wheel them out for
like a little a few words and or one of them I don't know on Woodrow Wilson but
FDR but who's who is his wife oh Eleanor so yeah Eleanor Roosevelt also I think
Did a lot of the duties he had Asperger's Joe you like hey Miguel. How are you? Thank you. Thank you for like yeah
Well, I don't know. I try to I think politics are very divisive and controversial and
It can be yeah, I'm for the most part. It's usually not good. It's like
Panel rules. It's like bar rules, you know, no religion no politics. Yeah
Yeah. Well, yeah, I don't do politics here. I don't do politics here. And it's like, you know, but as for religion, you know, I do, you know, the occult, which is like kind of the esoteric side to all religions and kind of all religions kind of kind of come together there.
And so it's not too controversial where it's like talking about, oh, this religion is superior. It's because it's all about all about just presenting a lot of
The different different things and having a discussion, but I just I don't like the debate about religion. Yeah, it has beta and her friend come back to
Let me see to hide a on denison again yet. Hey on denison lol
So yeah, to be this mad at you. You know, you know why beat as mad at you denison or no
no
No, I see that they were I came over here the other morning and you weren't here psych, but um
Uh, Bita and Rain were picking on Denison and I kind of felt bad after a little while because I was listening to some of stuff that Denison was saying was like, well, Denison's a cool guy.
No, I'm gonna run into Denison so I can come in and talk to you.
Yeah, I never, like I'm just-
Then you called me a gentleman.
Did.
Well, yeah.
You are well, you're really nice on my panel. You're perfectly well-behaved and respectful. No, I am thank you. I appreciate it
That was I did I do do politics on panels though. So how do you do?
Oh, yeah, I don't I get called a gentleman I get called a communist or a socialist
Lately it's communist and socialist
You know, sometimes it's even conservative, you know, that's not the first time I've been called conservative
right wing
ultra-nationalist I get all across the spectrum and
That's my favorite one
Oh, according to the eight-point test, I don't know if anybody's taken that but it's I don't really think of myself as fitting in a category
But how my current views would be categorized is probably social Democrat
Which is usually how I test
you
I'm I come out to like a well, I don't know if I've taken that one, but I
Am I I ascribe to like the libertarian philosophy of like
Actually, I actually fought more on the lines of
But I am Republic. I'm a registered Republican because they won't let you register as a libertarian, but
But my my views line up more with Libertarian views, you know, I
Basically give a shit what everybody wants. Just keep that shit away from me
You want to drive you want to dress up?
As a Chewbacca and stick your dick in a toaster and call out your wife. That's fine
Do that shit somewhere else?
Well, not yeah, not in your house, but you know in there all the time, right?
Do that shit over there you don't
I don't want to have to dress up as anything
I know well, I have a Chewbacca costume and but I just need I just need a new toaster
I might burn out my old one by fucking it too much. I'm just kidding
Okay, so I think you would have been a lot nicer to Denizen if you saw how extremely good looking you
Oh, you're hot
Hey Lawrence is fucking around. Oh, you sound you sound very attractive. I'm just gonna just get I'm not I'm not trying to hit on you
But yeah, you are in a gay gay bands panel, but I'm basically like a I'm harmless. I just joke
You're not wet I'm not gay Denison. Oh, I know I know
But I'll refrain from it, but you know, all I have to do is hear you're hot and I'll probably start hitting on you.
So I'll refrain though, you know. Irrespectful, I'll try to be respectful.
Yeah, kind of a rare, I'm kind of a rare breed on this panel verse, you know.
But I've always, I've always, you know,
I've been around mostly straight people all my life. My parents were actually straight, you know
My best friend is straight
And so yeah, and I get along with all kinds of people I hung out with you know gangsters and
Not too many gay people though. I really haven't come across too many gay people
It's kind of surprising in Los Angeles where you know pretty much almost everyone's gay
But actually like the real flamboyant and I I
kind of stayed away from like the parades and the and
The casual sex they seem to have a lot of casual sex not really
I'm like more into like looking for the Prince charming on the white horse
to come find me. So, I'll be waiting forever probably. Hey,
you got a sleuth ball. I'm a serial monogamous.
Yeah, it's just like too easy to hook up. The hook up culture in the gay world is
outrageous. It's like, because basically, it's just like, you can have sex anytime,
you know, anytime you want. There's plenty of
You know fish in the sea for gay people because you know gay guys are there's no buying dinner or anything
It's just straight to the point and then it's like hey bye. Never never talk to you again. It's very
Makes it made me not like men too much, you know, so I went some uh, I do want to fall in love
So I'll wait around for that. I'm I had a bad experience on grinder last year or this year last year
Yeah, pretty bad experience on grinder. And so I'm done. I'm done. I'm done with dating. I
gotta
Don't even even the ones that those dating apps and stuff. I was talking to somebody else last night about this like
I've even used the ones that you pay for like the match calm and stuff. I mean not I haven't used them a lot, but I'm just
It's you can't find good. You can't find good people on the internet. It's no, that's not true. It's hard to find
Give people on the internet, no matter what, even on the dating site, they're just not serious about, it seemed like to me, I couldn't find people that were serious about some things that I was serious about.
And I don't know, I would, I would say if you're going to do, if you're going to try to meet somebody that way, maybe do like.
Continuing education classes or like those meetups where you, you know, the others where you like go somewhere to a cooking class or something and like, yeah, I would just, you know, this, this seems like a more quality way to me a partner people on the internet seems like a lot of them are like, not.
Not able or just don't get out into so like the real world social scene and so it's or and so it's been it's like
It's really easy and a lot of people grew up. I grew up when I was a 14 with the AOL and it's hooking up with people
Make it it's easy to not make it real when there's an element of
of game to it anyway like there's an element when it when it feels like some city, it's not real, right?
Yeah, and it and it's easy for people to have online relationships because you're like, well, I'm still having a relationship
but it's without all of the
The things the relationship things that are important relationships. So yeah, I, um, I would, I would suggest something like that, like that. Cause that's fun. And you get an opportunity to meet people in a safe setting.
Yeah, well, with gaze is harder because it's like, there's not that many. So it would have to be like, you know, kind of a gay meetup or like, you know, a gay club. There's one gay bar. I think in the whole, um, South Bay.
Your whole the whole state I used to live I used to live on the way West Coast
You got a majority of the state. Come on
There's a lot. There's a lot of gay people out there. Yeah, I'm sure there are I'm not I'm introverted
The most I met the most people I have ever met on doing my show the most I've had on the most people
I've had the most socializing and that's only been the last six months. I'm 44 years old. So
If I don't not very good at socializing or
Picking up on social some social cues. I'm not very experienced in it. I'm still learning, but that's okay
But I'm doing okay. I'm doing okay. I'm very much a loner
and
Well, it's like you you've come out of your cell a lot since I met you
We're just you know
You are you are?
You you were just a quiet guy. I still liked you. I still thought you were cool
But you come out a little bit. That's good. That's gross
Because now I can go out in public and it's like and I never would be able to be able to look people in the eye
I never said hello. I just would always like trouble by people now. I'm like even if I don't have the camera
I'm like very friendly waving. Hey talking to people on the street
Look into dogs. You know, just I was out there. I don't know. You saw I got my speed in a speedo
Last week on stream for like a few hours and I know I'm waiting for I'm waiting for fourth of July
So I can put my up my little tennis. Yeah, we can Matt
That'd be great. Yeah, I guess I'm not shy anymore though. I think I think my shine. I think this show has killed my shyness and
Yeah, people do that for you. I
Used to be a nice respectable girl that never cost anybody out and now I'll tell a motherfucker to get back real quick
Yeah, I'm learning I'm learning more to stand up for myself. You know, I'm like kind of a little bit of a pushover
I'm a very forgiving and very loyal. It's like if I'm loyal to somebody. I'll I'll be loyal
Even if they hate me, I'll be loyal to them for life, but I'm a capricorn. It's a capricorn trait very loyal
Yeah, so good then again, it's like
This this year there's been so many close friends I've just
I don't know. I just don't know what happened. They get mad at me. I do maybe I got too drunk or something like that
But I would tend to wake up in the morning have people mad at me someone would send me a screenshot of what I said
I'm like, okay. Well, I was drunk, but
I'm trying to be funny, but well, okay, we I think people I think people on the internet
I think people on YouTube especially have a real
weird fascination
with
Holding people accountable for being fucking people and they soar things away and they you know
It's like the standards of people on YouTube for some reason you're held to some higher standard of living on YouTube
Like you have to account for all your sins. You basically an AA every panel you walk into hi
My name is Janice. I once called somebody a pedophile even though it wasn't true
People who remember shit like you said this you called me a bitch eight years ago
Come on get over it were adults their words did I try to hurt that hurt your feelings did I you know?
Physically harm you in any way. No, I didn't so you know exactly. That's why I say I always say okay
I like when people get mad at me over stuff
I'm like you act like I kicked your dog or something like you know, I did like you know
It's something like it's a horrible sin. I feel like I need to go to church and repent or something for
for you know, but you're cute like
Don't know
Friends when friends fight and you know the YouTube thing. Yeah, I think people think people hold
I didn't hear anything. Did you guys do anything? No, okay?
Well on YouTube hold each other accountable way too much
but as far as friends go when it you know you and Peter are friends and
I think that when things like that happen, I think it's a
It's a circle. I think it's a it's a it's an opportunity for growth
And I think that it is you know the Lord's way of taking you apart from each other
So you can grow and figure out your things and then y'all will be friends again
Hey, I'm so yeah, I want to it's hard. I well
It's like I can't it seems like I can't like rationally have a discussion rational discussion
And then I'll like I'll like if I talk like that's when I talk to her that's few times
I would like let her talk and then and then I did be to be to be to like trying to say something and then finally when she's
Stopped talking I start talking that she hang up on me and I'll be like, okay. Well, I
Didn't go out. You know, I didn't hear the word you heard the word restart now. Fuck yourself blackout and you know, it was you
I'll be okay, Andy. I'll be okay. I think I got I got you on time got your ass
Okay. I didn't eat anything. I heard something about it. I fixed it. I fixed it. I fixed it.
Yeah, why is this up? Oh
I'm sorry. I guess cuz that's some asshole. Oh, I'm shy. Oh, I thought you were like afraid of my face
Somebody came. Oh, let me see. Oh, no, I've seen that page before. What were you reading the giant ass?
What was that all about the giant ass?
Oh, it's called the goal. It's not called the golden ass. Oh
At the latest yeah, not the giant ass. That's a different book
Yeah, but it's a giant ass is a great book though. It's about a man who gets turned into a donkey accidentally and then he was like
It's a picture book
It's not a picture book. It's a it's a it's like the first novel of a written
It's a Roman novel written. I think in like maybe like 100 AD or something like that
You know who has a golden S. Jen has a golden S. I do Jen. Oh
Yeah
All right, she's right. I was being I was being nice
I wouldn't say golden. I'd say maybe so maybe bronze of a bronze. Yeah. Well, let me see. Okay.
So here we go. It's a really good book though. Really good book. Yeah, I was getting to one side
over there. What do you mean about the summer stuff? I don't know. Yeah, I don't know anything
I love summer. Summer's awesome. Summer's Eve. I don't think I've met summer. I don't know who she is.
She's been on my panel several times. She has the red hair, or she changed her hair color. She used to have red hair, but she has that red hair?
No, that's I think that is Marcy you're talking about. Marcy Fox. Which one's summer?
Summer. She's like, hey, fuckers. You always come and say, hey, fuckers. It's summer. She was on tonight a little bit earlier.
She's really cool. She's super cool. She's if you see him tonight. She just got a jail. I think
What's up JT right
Now that you guys have said so much about summer all I can think is I can I
Okay, that movie frozen when the little snowman when he sings that song about summer
That's what I've got going in my head right now. Oh
Little snowman see my summer. Well, yeah, not a good time for snowmen summer. I guess
Yeah, what a what a quote is silly so man, why don't you want to live in summer? But uh
Yeah, well, yeah, so it was just a summer solstice. I was thinking like yesterday was just such an intense intense energy day
And I read a little about the summer solstice and it said oh, it's a good day to balance energies and I say okay. Well, I
Think that the solstice I thought the solstice was on 23rd
There's a 20. I think it's 21st. I think I said the 20 to the 20 think you're right. Yeah. Oh shit. I missed it
Yeah
It was yesterday. Yes, and you pull the Sun card for me. Remember, right?
Oh, by the way, it's also it's when the Sun is closest to the Earth. I think the Sun is close. Oh, it's the 21st
That does explain everything
I didn't even realize it was I mean I kind of forgot but then I thought oh why is everything so crazy right now
It's and things sometimes are crazy around
The gastrological base exactly psych you pin the tail on the donkey right there
In the golden the ass. Yes
So, maybe we're going forward or back to normal, then that happens again.
Not quite.
Well, it happens to happen next year, but we are, I think there are some unique placements
for us the rest of the year.
There's going to be some, I think there's one, one, one, there's like some kind of
shrine or something of these three planets that hasn't happened since 1968.
And so every time one of those happens, there's, well, there's going to be great upheaval
in September.
Just be ready for that.
I know that.
It's a great great upheaval inside information
There'll be a lot of tumult
What do you have any inside information or is it? Yeah, I'm telling you the tumult. There'll be a lot of tumult on the
So it's you're saying don't need a house that day or that month
Oh, you can leave the house, but just don't any do any heavy traveling. You know what I mean? Okay, don't fly anywhere
Yeah, it'll be a lot of geomagnetic storms
So you're gonna ban my channel, right?
Am I going to bed? Who banned the channel about channel my what do I mean to say my my account or account?
Are you gonna ask nicely and promise to behave yourself and of course I guess
I've always been behaved
Okay, well, I'll give you another chance, you know, I don't listen. I know people are always talking about me to you
But no, no, I mean, I don't really listen to what people say about people
I always like, you know, I don't have time to go go verify it
I know but but you know, I do just pay attention to what's happening in my chat and stuff like that and to sir
It's a certain thing. I just haven't quite. There's some certain things that kind of like
Kind of like make the hair stand up on my back like a cat, right? I knew he was gonna say that
So it says psychic these two new panel guys sound sexy. Oh guys. You got a fan like Lawrence thinks you guys sounds guys Lawrence
I'm sorry. I think they're
I'm not gonna lie man, I have a lot of people that don't like me. I'm sure that that's probably obvious to you
But you know, I I'm decent with people who are nice to me
They don't like JT and Goddy because they're jealous because they think they're still in high school and they think they're still in high school and they think they're still in high school and they think they're still in high school and they think they're still in high school and they think they're still in high school and they think they're still in high school and they think they're still in high school and they think they're still in high school and they think they're still in high school and they think they're still in high school and they think they're still in high school and they think they're still in high school and they think they're still in high school and they think they're still in high school and they think they're still in high school and they think they're still in high school and they think they're still in high school and they think they're still in high school and they think they're still in high school and they think they're still in high school and they think they're still in high school and they think they're still in high school and they think
No, I don't think people
People only hated people what they it's like it's all it's always like a kind of big reflection of themselves like what wait
It's like something that they don't like about themselves
numerous people like I hate you
Thank you, what you don't understand is they hate him so much that they followed him all the way over here
And we're talking about 20 people followed him
All the way over here
How did they find out who told them about him being here
But I mean how did Hannah like find you exactly Hannah's the one that's Hannah was here
I know
She was actually in this channel before I was wait wait wait he asked the question answer his questions
How did Hannah find the 20 people we know and bring them here answer that question for him JT?
Oh, well, she she found them from Las Vegas live chat, right?
Las Vegas JC. These are all other
Psyche and told them all to come here and give JT shit
That's what you're not getting. I mean, I really I really haven't seen that too much of that. The only thing I'm doing people
I really listen
You haven't noticed anybody complaining about me
Um, I mean, I think that you know a few of some of my mom
And then they'll do that when you're posting that they're like he's posting weird videos and this is
They're like, it's just weird. I don't they're and they're saying they're kind of
Point of the point that I was making
Yeah, I know you've made the point and you've talked about you said oh it's legal to do that
Because I say I'm not even saying like oh, I'm pushing a boundary. No the point was the guy showed his own
he showed his own kids on i know i know i know people people people show their kids and you
should be able to understand that dude you're trying to make people i know and i know it's not
even that and but i wasn't the one to bring that's anybody's attention it's just like i you know
i didn't come in here talking about that it's not it's not like some cute little innocent
thing i mean it's like you know you're trying to mess around it says i understand it's like but
it's like just not the thing is the thing is it doesn't have anything to do with this
People
Doesn't but you but you guys kind of have nothing it's like to do with this channel like you know, I mean, it's like other than you know
I mean, yeah, you
What are you stuttering about psyche God? You know God got me like Sarah. It's just like it just seems like you know
It's like you're here for some purposes other than
Look at this cool show. It's like, I don't know. I don't know why you're here exactly
But you know, it seems like I just what do you do you think I'm here for some ulterior motive because somebody told you that like really?
I don't know. It's like you but you I don't know are you a big fan of your big family
I don't know. I don't feel like you'd like me very much. You know, I don't I feel like you don't trust me
No, it's like trust is something that's earned is not just given freely or else it can be like, you know
I feel as though you already have a certain oppression of me based on what you've heard about me
That's what I feel
No, I really I mean I was really I'm really like really skeptic. I mean I gave you two chances of the mod
I really did I mean I'm asking to be a mod forget the mod thing. I don't care about that
I know you're not asking, but I did give you even give you two chances for that and then it's like then you were like
Then you said oh your weak psyche and I saw some other stuff being said
I don't know if it was a joke or you're just trying in it or just trying to like, you know
Oh, you mean the tongue-in-cheek about the oh phase one phase do all that crap. Yeah. It was a joke psyche. Yeah
I mean that I mean that's not that's not very kind
It's not it's like it's like not really a joke cuz it's like, you know joke is like you really think I'm talking to people here to
Talk shit about me. You really think that why would I bring anybody here to talk shit about me?
I'm just saying like I didn't really see many people talk
I see a lot of people like you know, let that know you guys and like you guys and you know
Everyone loves gaudi, of course, you know not most like a lot of them do look like a JT too
They seem like you let they like you I mean I say I don't think people dislike you. I don't I just don't think some of the
like some of the stuff that's going on it just it's like you know what stuff is going on I don't
well you know they didn't I have to like I think what he's trying to say is people don't like what
you're doing and they're running and tattling to psyche about it and it's making psyche
difference what I do on my channel it has nothing to do with psyche yeah but that's what I'm saying
I was like I mean if you were to promote just your channel link that'd be fine if you just put
You keep posting that particular clip and then you're they open or the and they open it up and it's like yeah
Because I have like numerous people and they're trying to slander me about that clip
Well, it's not there's nothing this is not really the plate the plate unless you can say hey
You check out my channel if you're or something like that this their channel, but I respect that there's nothing wrong with that
I don't I mean
The thing is like
Yeah, I'm not I'm not even asking to be a mod. I really don't care about the mod thing
No, no, no worries, but it's like yeah, and I don't I mean I like you guys here and it's like
It's just you know, I'm I'm an intuitive and I I'm I just think you know, I just have to go with my gut
Like when I got says don't trust to me
I didn't say don't trust you it says
It says you know what watch this guy just watch it. What's what watch them a little bit? You should do
Exactly you should be you should be cautious of anyone. Yeah
About me though, I mean you're what you're one. I mean, there's many people that I get these feelings about right?
And it's like yeah, I know that's what that's for the thing. It's like I was
If I feel like
Like I like I got a 24 time 24 hour for saying something that I don't think even warranted that when I see
Numerous people talking mad shit about me all the time including mods. I don't say anything about it
But when I'm getting you know when I get timed out. I'm like and you're like
oh i trust my mods yeah well that was that was last night because sassy scarlet like you guys
were all saying i was reading the chat when you like you know all you guys were saying the same
stuff you know playing little play on words with uh you know say making all these references and then
sassy scarlet said please stop with the talk and then you kept going and so then she's been
in sassy scarlet's been one of my first mods and she's a great mod i understand you like her i get
I've had her with me for like, you know, probably six months or and she's she's you know, here a lot so
I understand that and I don't take that personally
How don't we stop explaining the past and what can we do to move forward? How about that?
We're moving forward we're moving forward so he understands you guys understand god and and uh, jt and rain or i've always
This is for you know, anybody that
It's like okay, I mean and this is for actually everybody, but I'm just telling you because I had this issue please. Okay, please do not
Change your picture to somebody else's picture
In my chat, I don't want you to do that. Please. That's again
Yeah, and then please and please
No clams or oysters
No more and what else like you
Um, you know, just to respect the rest of the rules, you know, just be respectful to the in the chat
If you I mean if you don't don't just fight with people in the chat, like, you know, if Hannah's in the chat
You can you can you can block Hannah in the chat so you don't see her. I don't ever see Hannah
Yeah
That's what I'm saying like all the people if you are if you're ever looking at your I get the impression
You look at your chat, so you can't really faint ignorance on that is
Ignorance is pretty
For example look at easy down they're talking bullshit
Right supposed to bring up that he stabbed Eli on the fucking streets, and we're supposed to not gloss over things like that
Come on, man, right. It's like anything said
right attacking back
But is this separate is that really even relevant? I don't know. I don't it just happened. It just happened. That's why it's relevant
People are in your ear about me. I think I
My show is not for people to come attack. I mean, I say people do and
Yeah
If I'm getting talking down for any little thing and you see people are constantly shitting on me
I'm not saying anything about that. It's about moving forward. That's all I know and we're trying to move forward
But this let's move forward
Yeah, and it's like, you know what it's like I'm
I don't I have nothing I have nothing against you and it's like you know, I see people have conflict
I have nothing to do with the conflict. I don't know the history there might have they might have done something to you
This might have been going on for a long time
People are allowed to mention my name and kids and stuff. That's totally okay, but I
Know right, I mean if they do if they do that they do that
I will if I see that if there's you do it though. I mean, I'm not like shit. No, that's not usually
I don't read the chat very carefully like it because there's a lot in the loud trolling
and I'm on the panel but last night I went off the panel and I was just watching because I there's
this weird stuff going on the chat and so I saw that on the chat and I would but I wasn't I still
wasn't watching on my phone where I was I see the mod activity I was just watching it on the
streaming our backstage and so
I didn't I brought some out and I was like, you know, I'll let
Just like last night it was just seemed like a night where I needed to like show that my mods
You can't just like oh, they discount my mods and stuff like okay
Well, your mods aren't very careful about it when anybody brings up kids and me though
If I ever see it you tell you tell me for you tell me if you say hey look what the person said
And mod or I will delete it. I mean, it's like I mean, I don't really feel like I have my I'm not really gonna run up
About it, but it's like
I mean it's like you're saying, oh my god, they're saying this about me
But you're doing the same thing that people and so it's like, you know, how about you not do that and then maybe
That's what I'm saying, I can't go into it you're all like, you know, it's like
Okay, well, well, I'll just ask it's like if it's like
If the show if the chat bothers you too much, maybe it's not the right show or chat for you. Okay, it's like, you know
You're pretty much here. Okay. I'm gonna say I know you're not I'm seeing you're welcome here
But it's like, you know, if you're so bothered by it
To me they should apply to everybody. Yes. Yeah, but okay, but I can't I can't I'm not I'm not like I only have
Stuttering listen listen to me. Don't tell me to stop stuttering. Okay. First of all, I'm trying to get thought. Okay. I'm only one person
I'm running a panel. I'm trying to listen to panel
In every little word to make sure something isn't said that you know
I'm not asking you to micromanage Japan. I'm saying hold me to the same thing as you hold everybody else too. That's all I'm saying
There's a lot of mods I see I see sassy scarlet's here. Good morning sassy. Okay. Nick is here
Okay, so and I think I found nothing wrong. So so you got time enough for 24 hours. You know any fucking cats
I've been I've been banned from I'm not gonna go
Did I make a big deal about that? No, I didn't
No, but I mean, yes, you you can't yes you you like kind of guilt ship me
You um, you like you're um, you know, I don't know what happened was
And what's happening is like I'm being held to different standards and when I bring it to your attention you say I trust my mods
I do have different I have different standards for my mods or my mods are they they have things that are like I expect my mods to
Support my channel and my channel. I don't expect
Person vendetta's and so that's why you're not a mod and also my mods are also I press them because
It means that I trust them that they're mad so they've been here longer
Most of them and they know what I want and I don't want that's been one of my rules
There's no pdf talk in the chat. She told you
She didn't hide you come to come here for 24 hours
And the point is my point is if there's no pdf talk my name is constantly mentioned
in pdf
Okay, but you know do you play around with like this I mean the people that are doing that
You like you're fighting with people are doing this and you can come if you're a community of people that do the same thing
And so I don't understand why that you're showing a double standard because you're doing the same thing to people
You're saying people are doing to you
Why are I let's do to them nobody's allowed to do it. So I'm telling my mods, please
If you see any doxing, any doxing, and look out for anyone.
If anybody, don't break any of them out there,
they should be held at the same standard I am.
Yeah, that's all I'm saying.
Anybody, like anybody that doesn't...
Okay, because I haven't seen that so far.
That's all I'm saying.
Yeah.
Okay, well, you know, sometimes there's more or less more. I can imagine you've been looking at your chat
You haven't seen my name show up numerous times with this and I get 20,000
There's 20,000 chat comments today. Okay, and that's like and I've trained myself not to read
Many of them like because it's like I can only read so many and plus. There's a lot of trolls that are just talking shit about me and other people
Because I already told you I said I'll unlock you and you're like and then you're but you're now you're like
Oh, well, what about this? What about this? What about this? It's like, okay?
I'm saying one thing only like I just
I think it's genuinely hard. I think it's genuinely hard for most people to treat everybody
The same well, I mean I want I mean I will I want to but you have to understand like you know
He's new and it's like he just came out of nowhere. Everyone's kind of like
That's why your girl is ugly as fuck.
Have I ever
You got to do taxes.
That's all you do.
Get off the panels.
Stop complaining about other panels.
That's why they don't look like you do.
Like, damn, Monica, you complain about stuff.
Move on.
You don't have to be here, papa.
You see what I'm talking about?
channel. Oh, my nigga.
Oh, you do.
That's what you do. That's what
you're doing now.
Oh, my God.
Say it, say it, say it, say it, say it, say it, say it, now you don't like it, you don't like it because you call people to me out, oops.
Nigga all y'all weirdo
Ziggy all y'all
Y'all y'all was gonna do something
Don't put your parents in danger for for the internet nigga
That's a rain in Texas though, right?
Oopsies
And it's called People PDF
I think you're docking something
Fine John
You think you're docking something right now?
Mind your business and watch your eyes
Little faggot
I'm magic complaining of psych all day
You gonna beat us damn it
They come back and they complain about psych
All day
Just jump off
This is ear cancer
Whatever it is I talk to you psych
Shout to you psych
I said, I said, I said, I said,
Fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck
Thank you everybody, have a good night guys!